Good morning night city
It's sunny and breezy today with gentle winds blowing
I'm just kidding
Let's get back to business
The night city
Government's life for supplies
Program is effectively narrowing the wealth gap and guiding night city
Toward a bright tomorrow
This is night city news
We'll see you in the next broadcast
在这儿味道的饱足感是有代价的
你吃下的每一口都是在嚼碎自己的明天
不啊
♪ Knee ♪
♪ I'm bleeding through the rusted rain ♪
♪ The scales of justice ♪
♪ Heavy with the pain ♪
♪ We're stopping for the truth in a world of love ♪
Look me in the eye of the old godi
♪ Judgment day is coming ♪
♪ Can you feel the heat the sound of revolution on a dead ♪
♪ End street ♪
♪ Give us back the soul ♪
♪ Break the iron crown ♪
♪ Where the fire runs in of the sun goes down ♪
各单位注意
7号区发生恶性抢劫事件
地点是永恒生命芯片店
别磨蹭
告诉我哪一个是重启芯片
不然我会让你和这玻璃一样碎成渣
别开枪
就是这玩意吗
已到达犯罪现场
各单位保持警戒
有后门吗
快告诉我啊
那那边
7号区嫌犯逃脱人质确认安全
已将嫌犯身份信息传于各单位
嫌犯正往荒坂大厦旧址方向逃窜
请求赛博特工支援
何必再做这无谓的反抗呢
啊你根本什么都不懂
什么你们这些被资本豢养的爪牙
永远不会明白我们在霓虹灯下活得有多窒息
真的是走投无路了
我不为谁卖命
但伤害别人从来都不对
哎那就只能这样了
呃没必要这样
我只不过是想救我女儿的命而已
这有什么错
呀呀呀嘿呀嘿
芯片拿出来吧
我会放你一条生路求你
那不是单纯的芯片
那是我女儿的命
要是人人都这样说
那夜之城岂不是乱套了
我是不会给你的
只有这个芯片能够重启我女儿的脑机
把芯片交出来
我会想办法去救你女儿的
你能有什么办法
我说过
我不服务于高层
我会想办法的
事已至此
我我只有相信你了
用一下高三闺女给我有太大
这件事我会搞清楚的
你死他到底经历了什么炼狱
这世界的心声原来是靠细看孩子的血来续命的
不管这混蛋藏在什么地方
我都要把他揪出来
呃呃你是谁
卫兵卫兵别喊了
都在地上躺着呢
你你要干什么
这可是内政大楼
我我是
我真的尽力了
芯片权限就3分钟
♪ Three minutes stolen from the master clock ♪
♪ While the unforce ♪
爸爸
我看见他们打你了
你还好吗
是爸爸没有保护好你
是爸爸对不起你
爸爸不能哭
你在我的世界里就是英雄
3分钟短到只是生命里的一瞬
光会消散
数据会清零
但这段重逢会被永远刻进芯片最深处
就算下一秒就要归于虚无
至少在这一刻
他们真正
♪ Of the humans in this hollow space ♪
♪ Oh i'll let the sky fall down on the neon street ♪